- Good night, Sheldon.
- Good night, Leonard.
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
- Hey, Leonard?
- Hi, Penny.
(Penny:)Hey, I just wanted to make sure
you were okay.
(Leonard:)I'm fine.
I am so sorry about what happened.
(Leonard:)It's not your fault.
(Penny:)Yes, it is.
That's why I broke up with him.
(Penny:)He always does stuff like that.
(Leonard:)So why was he at your party?
(Penny:)Well, I ran into him last week...
...and he was just all apologetic
about how he's changed.
(Penny:)He was just going on and on,
and I believed him.
(Penny:)And I'm an idiot,
because I always believe guys like that.
And I can't go back to my party
because he's there.
And I know you don't wanna hear this. I'm
upset and really drunk and I just wanna...
[SOBBING]